seair.co.in 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy - Seair.co.in

* When you use the [Seair.co.in](https://www.seair.co.in/) website, we collect the information sent through your devices such as computer and other mobile devices. We collect and store the information shared with us while using the website or services. 

* Information collected or stored is used solely to fulfill the purposes specified by us such as develop, deliver, and improve our services, verify your identity, or to protect you from fraud and prevent data loss. 

* We retain your personal information only for lawful purposes, wherever appropriate, with the consent of the concerned individual.

* Personal information provided should be complete, up-to-date and accurate to the best of your knowledge. 

* We may install cookies to your devices that help us to understand the user behavior. Information collected with the help of cookies is considered as non-personal. However, the identification of IP addresses is considered as personal. You can block cookies, but you may have to re-enter your user ID and password. 

* We use different measures to protect your information to eliminate the risks of unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, misuse or loss. We use data encryption technologies and firewalls to safeguard your information. 

* You have the right to provide personal data or not. When we collect information, we help you to make the choice. You don’t have to provide the information we ask, but you’ll have only limited access to our services and options. 

By availing the services of Seair.co.in website, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy. In case we’re making changes to our Privacy Policy, we will bring your attention to the changes made.
